Mihir Udaykumar Panchal

A/3, Rose Blossom, Sitladevi Temple Road, Mahim (W), Mumbai, Maharashtra,

Pin: 400016

Tel: +91 9819195358 Email: mihirpanchal4@yahoo.com Age: 25 Y

OBJECTIVE

Having 3+ years of Experience in - Mechanical & Electronic Industry. Knowledge in Manufacturing and Production processes with additional knowledge of analytical tools like SAS, Python and R. Keen to pursue a strong career in Data Analytics domain.

EDUCATION

2018 Grey Atom Data Science Engineering Program Mumbai, India

2017 Imarticus Learning Mumbai, India

• Diploma in Big Data and Analytics Mumbai

- Data interpretation and Analysis
- Understanding of Statistics
- Predictive Modelling
- SAS -Basic, Analytical tools- R and Tableau

2015 - 2017 Khar Education Society (K.E.S) Mumbai, India

• Bachelors in Science (Information Technology)

2008 - 2012 Larsen & Toubro Institute Of Technology Mumbai, India

• Diploma In Mechanical Engineering(Industrial Integrated)

2008 Gokuldham High School & Junior College Mumbai, India

• I.C.S.E (Standard - X)

ACADEMIC PROJECT

- Predictive Analytics on Ames housing data
- BSCIT: Final Year Project- Toll-Booth Systems.
- Diploma in Mechanical : Final Year Project- Remote operated Infra-Red Portable Forklift, using Single Screw Lifting Mechanism.

WORK EXPERIENCE: 3+ Years

2012 - 2015 Low Ohm Components- Pune Role: Production Engineer

Responsibilities

- Responsible for handling production processes for low watt resistors: Winding, Coating & Capping, Tinning, Baking,
- Performing the appropriate Testing for resistors (including the Quality Control, Labelling)
- Maintaining Clients Records and Delivery Services as per regulatory requirements.

2010-2010 Larsen & Toubro - EBG(SDDC) Role: Inplant Trainee

2011-2012 Gilbarco Veeder Root - Sales & Field Trails Role: Inplant Trainee

ACHIEVEMENTS:

- Inter-College Head in L.T.I.T-2012, Won College Basketball Competitions
- Event Facilitator at Kidville-Mumbai, Millk-Mumbai, Intern/Actor- BHARMA (Mumbai)

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Playing Online Computer Games: CS-GO, DOTA 2.
- Playing Cricket, Football, Table-Tennis.